

ANTONIO SERTIĆ

Software Developer

About Me

Software engineer with experience in creating creative and comprehensive applications for Android, desktop, and web. I work well in a team and readily take on delegated tasks. I appreciate feedback and enjoy suggesting innovative and creative solutions.

(+385) 091 545 9920

sertic43@gmail.com

16.12.1999.

portfolio website

in/antoniosertic

SKILLS

FRONTEND

- HTML, CSS (Bootstrap, SASS)
- JavaScript (AngularJs, Angular, Vue)

BACKEND

- NET
- PHP
- Java

BAZE PODATAKA

- SQL
- MySQL
- NoSQL

JEZICI

- Engleski (B2)
- Croatian (Native)

WORK EXPERIENCE

<u>Infigo</u>

Zagreb

Oct 2023 - Present

Learning Python & Splunk and their syntax.

Financial Agency (Fina)

Virovitica

Oct 2020 - Oct 2023

Project implementation from start to finish, designing and developing application architecture. Creating responsive applications and UI components. Manual testing of web pages. Working with agile methodologies. Writing modern, efficient, and sustainable code in the .NET development environment (Blazor, Razor Pages, JavaScript, SQL)

EDUCATION

Veleučilište u Virovitici

Bachelor of Computer Engineering Oct 2018 - Sep 2021

INTERNSHIPS/COURSES

Factory

Student Internship and Frontend Academy

Jul 2020 - Aug 2020

<u>Algebra</u>

Fundamentals of Agile Development and SCRUM - Seminar

Apr 2022

<u>Udemy</u>

Vue - The Complete Guide

Sep 2022

JavaScript - From Zero to Expert

Present

Python - Pro Bootcamp

Present